[music]
[音樂]
&gt;&gt; It is 7:51
現在是晚上7點51分
at night.
。
I'm about to fly the red-eye home from
我即將搭乘紅眼班機從
San Diego
聖地牙哥
to New York City.
飛回紐約市。
Yeah.
是的。
&gt;&gt; Hi Casey.
嗨，凱西。
&gt;&gt; How are you doing?
你好嗎？
&gt;&gt; Pretty good. Pretty good.
不錯。不錯。
&gt;&gt; The red-eye from the West Coast to the
從美國西海岸飛往美國
East Coast
東海岸的紅眼航班從來都不是
an easy decision.
一個容易的決定。
You fly 6 hours back to New York City.
你搭飛機6小時回到紐約市。
6-hour flight plus a 3-hour time change
6 小時的飛行加上 3 小時的時差，
means you land in New York City at 6:00
意味著你早上 6:00 抵達紐約市，晚上
a.m. You leave at 9:00 p.m. You land at
9:00 離開。早上6點落地。
First hour is always a wash cuz they're
第一個小時總是很無聊，因為他們要
making announcements and stuff. Then you
發佈各種公告之類的。然後
have 4 hours here in the middle. Then
中間還有4個小時。然後，在飛機
the last hour before you land, they're
降落前的最後一小時，他們會
making announcements and telling you to
廣播提醒你
put your seat belt on. So this is a
繫上安全帶。所以這算是
wash. This here
扯平了。這
this is your sleep.
就是你的睡眠。
I'll sleep better if I brush my teeth
如果先刷牙，我會睡得更好
first.
。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音樂]
&gt;&gt; Thank you. Thank you.
謝謝。謝謝。  很
&gt;&gt; Nice to meet you.
高興見到你。
Take care.
小心。
&gt;&gt; You made his day.
你讓他今天非常開心。  我也很高興。  他很感激。
&gt;&gt; Well, how are you?
你好嗎？
&gt;&gt; I'm doing okay.
我一切都好。
&gt;&gt; Good.
好的。
Good. And you can make a welcome aboard
好的。您可以搭乘飛往紐約甘迺迪機場的
this trip with flight with service to
航班，開啟這段旅程
New York JFK. Place your baggage to see
。放置行李時，請將
place your larger bags up top and your
較大的行李放在上面，
smaller bags
較小的行李放在下面。
&gt;&gt; Now, the goal here is to sleep as much
現在，我們的目標是盡可能多地睡覺
as possible.
。  現在
It's 9:00 p.m. and I have like a really
是晚上9點。我的
big seat. I feel pretty good about my
座位特別大。我對自己的前景感覺相當不錯。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音樂]
[music]
[音樂] 還
&gt;&gt; Not bad at all.
不錯。  現在
It is 6:22 in the morning. I did not
是早上6點22分。我在飛機上
sleep at all on that plane, not for 1
一
minute. I just sat up watching movies
分鐘都沒睡著。我全程就坐在那裡看電影
the entire time.
。
I feel like I used to be able to sleep
我感覺我以前能
on planes, but I don't know. I don't
在飛機上睡覺，但我也不確定。我現在完全不在飛機上睡覺了。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音樂] 現在是
&gt;&gt; So, it's like 6:30 in the morning.
早上6點30分。
I have to sleep at some point today.
我今天總得睡一會兒。
But, I also have like work and stuff to
但是，我今天還有工作和其他事情
do today.
要做。
So, I don't
所以，我不明白。
This is the problem with flying on the
這就是搭乘紅眼航班的問題所在
red eye.
。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音樂]
&gt;&gt; Quick wake up run.
快速起床跑步。
&gt;&gt; Marlon, you stuck?
馬龍，你卡住了嗎？
&gt;&gt; No.
不，
I have a package for you, man.
我帶了個包裹給你。
&gt;&gt; For me?
為我？
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
是的。  好了
&gt;&gt; All right, I'm up here. You want me to
，我上來了。你想讓我
come down?
下來嗎？
&gt;&gt; I'll meet you up.
我會和你見面。
&gt;&gt; Okay, okay. I'll see you in a minute.
好的，好的。我一會兒就到。
Protein pretzels.
蛋白質椒鹽脆餅。
They're good. They're really good. Do
它們很好。他們真的很優秀。
you want to take some home?
你想帶一些回家嗎？
&gt;&gt; Never take a red-eye flight, man.
千萬別搭紅眼航班，兄弟。
&gt;&gt; I did it last night. I'm a zombie. Like
我昨晚做的。我是殭屍。就像
my brain right now, my brain is at 10%
我現在的腦子一樣，我的腦子現在只用了10%
right now.
。
&gt;&gt; I thought that
我以為
the airport runs 24/7, right?
機場是24小時營運的，對嗎？
&gt;&gt; And you got those clothes?
你買到那些衣服了嗎？
&gt;&gt; So, we have to stay outside of the
所以，我們必須待在
airport.
機場外面。
And then, we slept on the the the tables
然後，我們就睡在桌上，
and the
還有
&gt;&gt; Outside the airport?
機場外了？
&gt;&gt; Outside of the airport.
機場外。
I'm telling you, it was the worst thing.
我跟你說，這是最糟糕的事。
I didn't know that, you know?
我不知道這件事，你知道嗎？
&gt;&gt; You want to take the box?
你想把盒子拿走嗎？
&gt;&gt; Yeah, but I I probably come back and
是的，但我可能還會回來，
every now and again I'll break the uh
時不時地我會把
I'll break the office and come in and
辦公室弄壞，然後進來把
get it.
它拿走。
&gt;&gt; [laughter]
[笑聲] 見到你真好。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音樂]
[singing and music]
[歌聲和音樂] 太棒了
&gt;&gt; That was so good.
。
&gt;&gt; Thanks, man.
謝謝，兄弟。
&gt;&gt; All right, thanks. Good to meet you.
好的，謝謝。很高興見到
&gt;&gt; Nice to meet you.
你。  很高興見到你。
&gt;&gt; Got to the office, did several Zoom
到了辦公室，開了幾個 Zoom
calls, got my packages, got to hang out
會議，拿到了我的包裹，還
with Marlon.
和馬龍一起玩了一會兒。  明白了，花了差不多
Got It was like a full 2/3 of a day.
三分之二天的時間。
What?
什麼？
Not bad.
不錯。
Gridlock traffic everywhere. [music]
到處交通堵塞。 [音樂] 出事了
Something's going on.
。
What is this? What's happening?
這是什麼？發生了什麼事？
&gt;&gt; It's a
這是一場有益
run for heart health.
心臟健康的跑步活動。
&gt;&gt; Run for heart health. How far of a run
為了心臟健康而跑步。這段路有多遠
is it?
？
&gt;&gt; 5K.
5公里。
&gt;&gt; You going to wear the jacket?
你要穿那件外套嗎？
&gt;&gt; I'm walking.
我在走路。
&gt;&gt; You got this.
你一定可以的。
&gt;&gt; can I get a a picture real quick?
能馬上給我拍張照片嗎？
Quincy, nice to meet you.
昆西，很高興見到你。
&gt;&gt; Nice to meet you. 4 3
很高興見到你。 4 3
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音樂]
&gt;&gt; You guys are the best cheerleaders I've
你們是我見過的最棒的啦啦隊
ever seen.
。
&gt;&gt; we've been trying. Big fan, big fan.
我們一直在努力。鐵粉，鐵粉。
&gt;&gt; Come here, buddy, right [music] now.
過來，夥計，現在就過來（放音樂）。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音樂]